= kissasia.be =
Fu Mingyu's strength.
One.
He's tall too.
and good figure.
What else?
Oh no.
I really can't remember anything
I can't remember anything.
I can only think of his handsome face.
He can't talk.
cheesy lines.
I can only say semi-finished products.
Between confidence and arrogance,
with confidence and confidence.
I was always busy.
He doesn't have time for me.
emotional value
doesn't exist at all.
I still have
the ability
can piss me off.
In terms of emotions,
is quite stable.
He always has a long face.
Why on earth
be with him?
You used to take a flight.
You should know very well
what will happen.
Are you
to make an example for you?
I'm not here to plead for her.
I'm not asking you to set an example for me.
This is unfair.
That passenger...
He's a rogue in the air.
with a gold card.
God is coming.
Slippers, eyeshades,
carpet, pillow and wine.
Give him infinite supply.
I didn't want to disturb him.
I even gave him food in advance.
What else should I do?
And that day,
in front of Jiang Ziyue.
in the beginning.
He humiliated me first.
He even hit me.
It's good that we didn't call the police.
He's being unreasonable.
Why should he
fire the flight attendant?
We checked the CCTV.
Jiang Ziyue did say
harsh words.
And what she did before...
it's not too much
to fire her.
Why not?
When there is a safety problem,
the aircraft got off the plane.
Now when something happens,
he takes the blame.
If he has any unreasonable request,
any unreasonable request,
When the aviation driver
gave him the gold card,
Why restrict him?
Just let him sit in business class.
If
If the navigator
doesn't stand in the staff's shoes,
What about the sense of security
and sense of belonging?
What if I say
I fired her
for you?
For me?
For what?
When Boyang was investigating,
when you left Shihang,
all the rumors
came from Jiang Ziyue.
This kind of character
such a virtue.
Don't take this as an excuse.
Actually,
I knew it too.
I didn't repay you with kindness.
I just think
people are complicated emotional carriers.
Before I was hurt by public opinion,
I was also helped by her.
I don't know
but in my heart,
in my heart.
My relationship with her
is good or evil.
is our private matter.
Fu Mingyu.
Where's your personal and professional distinction?
Mine is professional.
If I separate my private life,
I wouldn't have
again and again?
You deny it.
I'm here to plead for her.
But today,
made me know you again.
I'm impressed.
Since you know
she did something behind my back,
Are you willing to
for such a person?
What if I were you?
What if
in the same situation,
Will you
try your best
to plead for me.
It depends on what it is.
But what can happen
in the world.
But
I promise you.
Promise what?
I'm not interested
between us.
I won't affect my work
and will never
because of work.
Can my girlfriend
can you
to have dinner with me?
That's an exchange.
You can think so too.
So beautiful.
Are you hungry?
Yes.
Hungry.
Order more later.
This way, please.
Okay.
Here.
Okay, thank you.
You're welcome.
Hello, Mr. Fu.
Is the order style
Still the same?
Is it light?
Thank you.
Give me the menu.
Okay.
Here.
See if you like anything.
Miss Ruan, excuse me.
Do you need my help
recommend our department?
Let me have a look.
Okay, no problem.
Order whatever you like.
This is too expensive.
There's a membership card.
We can get a discount.
When Ms. He came here,
when Ms. He came here?
Ms. He
would order our signature dishes.
Fry oysters with bee nest.
Red onion, spicy, red bean and red bean paste, east star spots,
Honey Braised Beef Steak.
Fried asparagus and lilies.
You're good at ordering.
Can I?
Yes.
That's all.
Okay, no problem.
Thank you for your order.
Here.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Mr. Fu.
Call me if you need anything.
I'm nearby.
Okay, thank you.
Okay.
Is Ms. He the one
You've seen
an important client of mine.
Come here often.
Are you jealous?
It was because of work.
This time is different.
This time
with my girlfriend.
So the food this time
better than before.
Boyang's call.
Let me answer it.
Hello?
Excuse me.
I'll serve you the first dish.
Yes, I'm outside now.
Can't you and Wang Lekang go first?
Okay.
I see.
I may
need some time.
Bye.
Is it urgent?
There are some
in the company.
It's okay.
I can eat alone.
Go ahead.
But I can't finish
I can't finish them all.
It's okay.
Since you've ordered,
Eat more.
Here.
I can do it myself.
I know you can.
But I want to do this for you.
Thank you.
The East Star Colour here is very delicious.
Other places
in other places.
You can't eat it later.
I'll tell the manager
you can bring back
You can take them back.
Okay, got it.
Go now. Don't delay.
There's no rush.
Take your time.
Tell me when you get home.
Take care.
I'm leaving.
I forgot something important.
Bye.
Hello.
Do you have an appointment?
No.
But can we sit in a private room now?
The room is full.
I'll try my best
a quiet place for you.
I told you to come earlier.
There's no good place for you.
No.
Why don't we go to another restaurant?
I want to eat here.
for a long time.
Then let's eat.
Sure.
This way, please.
Please.
He said he wanted to come here for dinner.
but you didn't order.
I didn't expect
there would be so many people.
And if you sit outside,
Maybe there will be more people.
Right?
Why are there so many excuses?
The food is delicious.
Please.
Thank you.
You can order more.
It looks like you have a lot of stuff, right?
This small table is also good.
This way.
You...
You're really noisy.
Go inside. You go.
Serve the dishes here.
Yes.
I'll make it dirty.
Ruan.
You're eating here alone?
Fu Mingyu has something to do and left.
That's great.
Let's eat together.
Why
always together recently?
As you can see,
We're together.
We tried dating.
Banana, come and eat.
This way.
Okay.
Good.
I need to use the bathroom.
Are you really together?
probation period.
Banquet.
There's a lot of love history.
You know that, right?
We grew up together.
What could happen to him?
I didn't know.
Can you accept it?
I
really think the banquet is good.
Look at him.
humorous,
Funny.
and emotional value.
And don't you think
he's handsome too?
handsome,
and handsome.
In my heart,
I think he's better than Fu Da Tou.
Look at him.
He left you
to eat alone.
He won't accompany you.
The banquet is different.
Whatever I do,
he's always with me.
Are you going abroad for too long?
I don't know him well.
My boyfriend
know my boyfriend from others.
Besides, Ruan,
you're talking
more and more like my mom.
Besides,
Fu is so good.
He has no dark history.
He has no bad habits.
The food you eat now
is paid by Fu Mingyu.
Talking about him while eating.
This is betrayal.
Stop eating.
You...
Waiter, pack up.
Why are you in a hurry?
My boyfriend bought this.
Ask your boyfriend to treat you.
You look
more and more alike.
So stingy.
Where are the dishes?
He left with someone.
Gone? Where?
Why did you leave?
You have to praise me.
I did something big just now.
Tell me.
I put you
with Fu Mingyu.
with Fu Mingming.
and saved your face.
Compared to Fu Ming,
I must be the best.
Come with me.
Order whatever you want.
The bill, please.
Mr. Fu.
Mr. Su came here temporarily.
Because tomorrow
tomorrow.
We don't have much time.
so I called you.
I know.
Fu Ming is better than a banquet.
He's much better than him.
All right.
Fu Mingyu's strength.
I want to list them for one day.
He's handsome.
than Bananan.
I'll write it down now.
What other advantages do you have?
Don't turn on the lights.
It'll be dark.
Besides, it would be bad
it would be bad.
That's more exciting.
Why is Ruan alone?
What is this?
Fu Mingyu's advantage list.
He's handsome.
Tall
Good figure.
Good kissing skills.
Who?
Well, excuse me.
Okay.
Wait, Mr. Fu.
A toast to you.
Thank you for your support.
OK, Mr. Su.
Here, Mr. Su.
Cheers.
Here.
Thank you for your support.
Same to you.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Here, Mr. Su.
Do you remember
Thank you very much
Yes, come on.
Let's have a drink.
Come on. Let's drink together.
Hello
Come on.
Together.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
for your support.
What are you doing?
Come on.
Come.
Mingyu.
About what I said last time,
is you, Fu Mingyu?
You are...
Me?
Li Zhiyai.
Don't you remember me?
Don't move.
This is a very serious plot.
We've come this far.
Why won't you tell me?
Jane!
I told you it would work, right?
All right.
I'm going to eat pollen.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
Okay, you eat.
So,
how good is his kissing skill?
Tell me in detail.
Don't just eat.
No.
You know it anyway.
You ate it.
You're soft-hearted.
After this meal,
after this meal.
Oh my!
Xiaozhen
We've made it.
living happily
with sisters.
Xuan, don't just say that.
Try it.
Okay.
Try this feast.
How delicious is it
The expensive ones are different
It's delicious.
Look at you.
If you don't eat this big meal,
I like to eat cheap food.
Didn't you see
just a little?
If I eat them all,
how can I bring them back to you?
It's for your own good.
Don't blame me.
Besides, I like this.
I like pollen.
Ruan is really generous.
But I have
a small problem.
Can you two eat together?
Why can't you eat together?
He's not bipolar.
We all eat the same food.
Almost.
This is too different.
I'll buy
I'll pay you 24 yuan.
I can afford
for his meal.
but I feel sorry for you.
I don't mean to pour cold water on you.
I think
two different consumers.
Don't you think
you're from different worlds?
One meal
after a meal.
There are people
for the rest of their life.
You don't know each other well.
But people with different views
can hardly be together.
We have different views.
It's hard to be together.
But we have different views.
It's not about eating differently.
Different
Different preferences.
He can be a white snow,
I can also be a Shachiba.
As long as he eats a big meal,
I don't think he's wasteful.
When I ate pollen,
he didn't think
I'm not good enough.
That's it.
In life,
if we can meet
who
a perfect match.
are indeed lucky,
but this world
there are no leaves
the same leaves.
No way.
there would be someone who's totally the same.
But even if he is different,
it's not a contradiction.
More
expands each other's boundaries.
Life
will become bigger.
Eat up.
Ever since the funeral,
she has
a different person.
I think she has lost a lot of weight.
Recently,
care about her lately.
Your chicken soup
is good for her today.
She's been talking about
she would never meet
like Lu Ming.
Coming.
Where are you flying tomorrow?
I'll fly for a while.
Chuncheng and Pingcheng
It's getting late.
Let's go.
Okay.
Jane
Do you want to stay here tonight?
No.
You have work tomorrow.
Let's take the trash away.
Okay.
Take care.
Call me when you get home.
Okay.
Stop calling.
Just send a message.
Bye.
Let's go. Take care.
What are you doing?
I'm thinking about the difference between us.
Where are we flying today?
Chunseong.
Okay.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Wait for me.
Okay.
Isn't it too cold?
Blow out.
Your alcohol test is successful.
It's not easy to get around.
We need to get ready.
Prepare for a long battle.
Don't say that.
Be careful of what you say.
Sehang 5949.
It's raining heavily in Chuncheng.
Reveal your intention.
OK. Sehang 5949 received.
Let's spin and wait.
Take a look.
Two weather conditions.
Copy that.
Captain.
First preparation.
The weather is good.
Okay.
Chunseong.
Sehang 5949.
Our oil
for more than an hour.
The weather hasn't improved.
we'll prepare for the smoke counter.
Roger. Sehang 5949.
Okay.
Please wait.
We have time to take off.
we will inform you
as soon as possible.
What's going on?
Gosh.
Please wait patiently.
I'm really sorry.
I have something to do.
I have an appointment.
Release Sehang 5949.
Check the order before taking off.
Camera 02, ready.
Sehang 5949.
Weather reasons. Line up.
You're the fourteenth.
It's estimated to take ten minutes.
Is it possible?
The time is not locked.
It's all anti-landing.
We have a lot of pressure.
Hello, Front.
I'm the flight attendant.
We expect
wait 140 minutes.
That long?
It's because of the weather.
We need to line up.
Roger.
We need the ground.
with some food and drinks.
What a pity.
I can't get out of the plane.
Sausage salvage from the airport
It's really fresh.
I didn't expect you
about food.
Enjoy your plane meal.
When will your plane
take off?
I'm sorry.
We're not sure
Can we check the time?
The weather
We really
can't be sure.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
Please wait patiently.
You can't just drink water.
Miss,
Your cabin
is so suffocating.
Open the door.
Let me get some fresh air.
Ma'am.
We can't open the door now.
How about this?
I'll get you some water.
Have some water.
Please wait patiently.
Excuse me.
How long will it take?
Are you leaving or not?
Are you flying or not?
My family is still waiting there.
What's going on?
Can we fly?
I understand
how you feel now.
Our plane
is already in line.
Please understand.
I can't.
Stay here.
for three hours.
I'm really sorry.
I have a meeting today.
Sorry.
for wasting your precious time.
Open the door.
Let's get off the plane.
If we open the door now,
we have to
in a while.
Please understand.
You always talk about the weather.
My wife said
it's not raining in Chunseong.
I'd rather take the train.
Sorry, sir.
I'm really sorry.
We should have bought the train tickets.
Now we’re here.
Hello, Captain.
I’m the flight attendant.
How many travelers
decided to cancel the schedule.
I can't persuade them.
They'll have to line up again.
Talk to them.
We've been waiting for an hour and a half.
Yes.
But I've said everything I can.
They still have to hang in there.
I'll call my family.
Okay.
I'll look for the local clothing.
I finally see hope.
It's okay.
You'll get used to it
you'll get used to it.
No.
Let him go.
Sehang 5949, get ready.
Sehang 5949.
The queue is estimated to take an hour.
My mouth...
I dare not talk nonsense again.
This is a waste of time.
Yes.
I have a lot to do today.
Me too.
Ms. Oh, come here.
Hello, sir.
How can I help you?
Don't you know what to say?
Didn't you just say
is about to take off?
Another hour has passed.
Sir.
Our plane
is already lining up to take off.
There are many flights left.
Please go back to your seat.
Please wait patiently.
Who has patience?
No patience.
Our patience
our patience.
Let me tell you.
you have to
give us an explanation.
You must give us an explanation.
Yes, I'm really sorry.
Fly faster.
There's another part.
Roger.
Choose quickly.
320.
Check.
Hello, welcome on board.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hello, welcome boarding.
Hello, sir. Welcome.
Hello, sir.
Welcome on board. Sorry to keep you waiting.
Welcome.
Sir, your seat is here.
Welcome boarding, kid.
Welcome. Sorry to keep you waiting.
Release Sehang 5949.
Do you have time?
Sehang 5949.
Look now.
The departure time is 1315.
The departure time is 9:15.
The plan we made
is two hours.
After 11:15,
Why don't you turn off the ski?
We’ll be late by 11.
Captain,
I think the national traffic system
the flight time is 1315.
The weather is not good.
The flight is overdue.
The company’s business flight is cancelled.
Okay.
Xiao Ruan.
Do you want to try?
Cancel the flight broadcast.
Okay.
Hello, sir.
I'm Ruan Siyuan,
of this flight.
We're sorry to tell you
due to the thunderstorm,
for your safety,
we have to
cancel this flight.
How can you cancel it?
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We've been waiting for eight hours.
How could you cancel it?
Sorry.
You're so unreliable.
What a drag.
Sorry.
What's going on?
Can we sue him?
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
You just apologized
just because you said sorry?
Do you know how many orders
because of you?
Can you afford it?
If I lose my job,
none of you can do it.
I'm really sorry, sir.
Stop laughing.
Are you laughing?
Stop laughing, sir.
Sir.
What's so funny?
Is it funny?
Smile
It's not funny at all.
What a drag.
Sorry.
Sorry. Take care.
But it's true.
Mom.
I really want to quit.
It's been a long day.
Because of
our smile service
You want to hit us?
How about asking this hotel
if there are any rooms left.
Forget it.
I've called this place, but they haven't.
I'm hanging up.
There are too many people left.
It's full.
Hello?
Where are you?
I'm waiting for a taxi.
I haven't found a hotel yet.
I gotta go.
Why didn't you tell me?
There shouldn't be a problem.
tell me right away?
Why are you here?
I was afraid my girlfriend would be too independent
and lacks presence.
So I came here.
Seriously.
You're getting more glib-tongued.
I sent you so many messages.
Why didn't you reply?
Can't you see I'm busy looking for a hotel?
Keep the change.
All the hotels nearby are empty.
Where are we going?
Everything is ready.
Well...
They...
I can only take care of you.
and everyone else?
Let's go.
Thank you, Mr. Fu.
What's wrong?
You want to speak but stop.
Nothing.
It feels quite magical.
An hour ago,
we didn't know where to sleep.
At this moment, do you think
being a boss's girlfriend
is actually quite good.
Boss.
Let me tell you something.
If one day
you don't like me anymore,
you must let me know.
Call me, tell me face to face.
or send a message.
Don't worry.
I won't pester you.
And I won't ask you for alimony.
But you...
I'll pay you double.
You can't go back on your word.
I signed it in the contract.
I also want to ask you
Why did you curse me?
We'll break up.
I'm just saying.
If one day
you don't tell me,
without telling me.
I...
You...
what you do.
I'm serious.
Why are you so close?
Let's get down to business.
we can get close.
I will
give you flowers.
The mourning hall is in the middle.
I think you don't want to
walk out of this small room.
I'm sleepy.
I want...
sleep.
Okay.
Sleep.
Where do you want to sleep?
I...
Go.
Well,
Ni Tong.
She’s too timid to sleep alone.
Good night.
Have a good sleep.
Bye.
Actually, I'm a coward too.
I won't let
what you said.
Captain Pu.
Mr. Bai.
Morning, Xiao Ruan.
Mr Fu has to go.
He asked me to prepare the car for you.
I'll take you to the airport first.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Everyone, thank you for coming with me.
There's a bus at the door.
You'll go to the airport first.
Okay, here.
He's angry.
What are you doing?
Pick oppa.
I like these guys.
Look.
One brother is not enough.
Of course not.
Prepare some flat shifts.
How about this?
It looks like you.
Then choose him.
As long as you change fast,
there's no sadness but love.
Love
Thank you for sending me to the train station.
It's okay.
On my way.
Why isn't he back yet?
Fu Mingyu.
I'm back.
Did you drink?
Come in first.
Slowly.
Slow down.
Why didn't you answer your phone?
Phone?
You made so many calls.
Sorry.
My phone.
in the fridge.
Here, drink this.
Snow hide
Snow hide phone?
or me?
Are you kidding me?
I kissed my phone.
Am I not your boyfriend?
You didn't kiss me.
You're still in probation.
Fu Mingyu.
He's asleep.
I've been waiting for you for so long.
but you fell asleep.
Who did you drink with?
What did you drink?
Why did you drink?
You won't say anything, right?
Yes.
That's right.
Don't tell me.
A man
Why are your eyelashes so long
This nose is so high
You should slide on it.
and rub it hard.
so that you can be arrogant all day.
Your lips
is also very soft.
No wonder it's so easy to kiss.
Look again.
I'll eat you if you keep looking.
Look at you.
who will eat who?
If you show off again,
I'll eat you up.
and throw you to the garbage station.
Which category should I throw?
Harmful trash.
Sa Kyung.
Promise me one thing.
What? What?
If you don't like me anymore,
you must tell me in person.
Don't text me.
or call me.
Tell me in person.
I know
what you don't like about me.
I can change.
But don't
as garbage.
Don't
abandon me.
If you don't wake up,
I will
throw you away.
Didn't we agree
not to throw it away.
Don't throw it away.
No.